<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<chapter>
    <title>Podstawowe informacje</title>
    
    <section>
        <title>Wymagania sprzętowe</title>
        
        <para>
            Jak każda aplikacja PHP, Coyote do działania potrzebuje interpretera PHP, w wersji 5.1
            (zalecana wersja 5.3.3). Przydatny może okazać się również serwer ;) Polecamy popularny
            serwer Apache 2.0.X (aczkolwiek projekt testowany był również w wersji 2.2.X). 
            Jeżeli Twoja aplikacja w domyśle ma korzystać z bazy danych, musisz
            zainstalować oraz skonfigurować odpowiedni system bazodanowy.
        </para>
        
        <para>
            <important>Do wersji 1.1, Coyote Framework obsługuje jedynie bazę MySQL oraz PostgreSQL.
                Jeżeli chcesz obsługiwać w swojej aplikacji inną bazę, musisz napisać odpowiednią klasę
                obsługi danych (adapter). Więcej szczegołów znajdziesz w dalszej części
                podręcznika.
            </important>
        </para>
        
    </section>
    
    <section>
        <title>Licencja</title>
        
        <para>
            Projekt oparty jest o licencję BSD-new, której treść znajduje się poniżej.
        </para>
        
        <para>
            <programlisting>
Copyright (c) 2003-2010, Adam Boduch
All rights reserved.

Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification,
are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:

* Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice,
this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.

* Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice,
this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation
and/or other materials provided with the distribution.

* Neither the name of Adam Boduch. nor the names of its
contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this
software without specific prior written permission.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS "AS IS" AND
ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED
WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE
DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT OWNER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR
ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES
(INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES;
LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON
ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT
(INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS
SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.            
            </programlisting>
        </para>
    </section>
    
    <section>
        <title>Autorzy</title>
        
        <para>
            Autorem wersji 1.1 jest Adam Boduch. Jednakże wcześniej wiele osób miało wkład w
            powstawanie projektu.
        </para>
    </section>
</chapter>